Connecticut Citizens Action Group Records 1987.0024
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XIII: Utility Rate Cases, undated, 1970-1990s
  - 1974-1979
    - Louise's Notes/Research (Box 102:, Folder 3481)
    - Low Income Planning Agency (LIPA) (Box 102:, Folder 3482)
    - Mailing Labels (Box 102:, Folder 3483)
    - Master Metering (Box 102:, Folder 3484)
    - Meter Accuracy (Box 102:, Folder 3485)
    - Michigan
      - General (Box 102:, Folder 3486)
      - Public Service Commission (Box 102:, Folder 3487)
      - Rates, 1974 (Box 102:, Folder 3488)
      - Rate Cases, 1974-1978 (Box 102:, Folder 3489-3493)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station (Box 102:, Folder 3494)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station Emergency Plan, 1979 (Box 102:, Folder 3495)
    - Motions to Dismiss: Northeast Utilities, 1977 (Box 102:, Folder 3496)
    - National Council for the Public Assessment of Technology (NCPAT), 1976 (Box 102:, Folder 3497)
    - Natural Gas (Box 102:, Folder 3498)
    - New Britain CAG (Box 102:, Folder 3499)
    - New Jersey Utility Rate Information, 1978 (Box 102:, Folder 3500)
    - New York Residential Insulation Survey (Box 102:, Folder 3501)
    - North End Utilities Action Group (Box 102:, Folder 3502-3503)
    - Northeast Utilities (NU)
      - General, 1974 (Box 102:, Folder 3504)
      - General, 1976-1979 (Box 103:, Folder 3505-3509)
      - Annual Reports (Box 103:, Folder 3510)
      - Applications, 1974-1975 (Box 103:, Folder 3511)
      - Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 103:, Folder 3512-3513)
      - Internal Documents (Box 103:, Folder 3514)
      - Land and Resource (Box 103:, Folder 3515)
      - Media, 1976 (Box 103:, Folder 3516-3517)
      - Rate Cases, 1970-1975 (Box 103:, Folder 3518-3525)
      - Rate Increase (Box 104:, Folder 3526)
      - Stockholders Meeting (Box 104:, Folder 3527)
    - Oregon Rates, 1974 (Box 104:, Folder 3528)
    - Originals: Fact Sheets, Flyers (Box 104:, Folder 3529)
    - Other States (Box 104:, Folder 3530-3531)
    - Pamphlets (Box 104:, Folder 3532-3533)
    - Phantom Taxes (Box 104:, Folder 3534)
    - Pierce Power Plane (Box 104:, Folder 3535)
    - Pipeline Refunds (Box 104:, Folder 3536)
    - Power Facility Evaluation Council (PFEC), 1978 (Box 104:, Folder 3537-3538)
    - Pre-1977 Shutoffs (Box 104:, Folder 3539)
    - Press Utility Organizing, 1976-1977 (Box 104:, Folder 3540)
    - Public Utility Control Authority (Box 104:, Folder 3541)
    - Public Utilities Commission (PUC) (Box 104:, Folder 3542-3543)
    - Public Utilities Control Authority (PUCA), 1977-1979 (Box 104:, Folder 3544-3551)
    - Public Utilities Control Authority (PUCA), 1977-1979 (Box 105:, Folder 3552)
    - Publications on Energy, 1975-1976 (Box 105:, Folder 3553-3554)
    - Publications on Utility Rates (Box 105:, Folder 3555)
    - Rate of Return (Box 105:, Folder 3556)
    - Rate Structure (Box 105:, Folder 3557-3560)
    - Releases (Box 105:, Folder 3561-3563)
    - Shutoffs, 1977-1979 (Box 105:, Folder 3564-3566)
    - Sign-in Sheets: Legislation, 1978 (Box 105:, Folder 3567)
    - Southern CT Gas, 1977-1978 (Box 105:, Folder 3568-3571)
    - SNET (Box 105:, Folder 3572)
    - Stamford/Norwalk, 1978 (Box 105:, Folder 3573)
    - Statewide and Regional Organizations (Box 105:, Folder 3574)
    - Statewide CCAG Utilities Coalition (Box 105:, Folder 3575)
    - Statewide Oil/Gas (Box 105:, Folder 3576)
    - Supreme Court, 1976 (Box 105:, Folder 3577-3579)
    - Survey of Residential Utility Costs (Box 106:, Folder 3580)
    - Taxes (Box 106:, Folder 3581)
    - Telephone Service (Box 106:, Folder 3582)
    - Ten-Year Forecast: Northeast Utilities, 1975 (Box 106:, Folder 3583)
    - Time of Day Rates (Box 106:, Folder 3584)
    - United Auto Workers (UAW): Utilities (Box 106:, Folder 3585)
    - United Illuminating (UI) (Box 106:, Folder 3586-3602)
    - Utilities (Box 106:, Folder 3603)
    - Utilities and Conservation Program (Box 106:, Folder 3604)
    - Utilities and Hydroelectric, 1976-1977 (Box 106:, Folder 3605)
    - Utility Action Conference (Box 106:, Folder 3606)
    - Utility Advocates Newsletter (Box 106:, Folder 3607)
    - Utility Conference (Box 106:, Folder 3608)
    - Utility Contracts, 1973 (Box 106:, Folder 3609)
    - Utility Energy Strategy Material (Box 107:, Folder 3610)
    - Utility Fact Sheets/Flyers/Memos (Box 107:, Folder 3611)
    - Utility Hearing: Northeast CT (Box 107:, Folder 3612)
    - Utility Materials (Box 107:, Folder 3613-3614)
    - Utility Publications (Box 107:, Folder 3615)
    - Utility Rate Structure (Box 107:, Folder 3616)
    - Vecinos Unidos (Box 107:, Folder 3617)
    - Volunteers: Environment (Box 107:, Folder 3618)
    - West Hartford (Box 107:, Folder 3619)
    - Western Massachusetts Electric Company (WEMCO), 1976 (Box 107:, Folder 3620)
    - Wethersfield (Box 107:, Folder 3621)
    - Wisconsin, 1977 (Box 107:, Folder 3622-3623)
  - 1980-1983
    - Abuse of Power: New Jersey PIRG Report, 1974 (Box 108:, Folder 3624)
    - A Rate Payer's Guide to PURPA, 1979 (Box 108:, Folder 3625)
    - CCAG Application for Intervenor Status re: CL&P (Box 108:, Folder 3626-3627)
    - Connecticut Light and Power (CL&P)
      - Cross Examination (Box 108:, Folder 3628)
      - Rate Increase Decision, 1982 (Box 108:, Folder 3629)
      - Staff Issue Papers, 1982 (Box 108:, Folder 3630)
    - Electric Utility Rates Reform (Box 108:, Folder 3631)
    - Energy and the Environment (Box 108:, Folder 3632)
    - Legislative Bills, 1978 (Box 108:, Folder 3633)
    - Millstone III, 1982 (Box 108:, Folder 3634)
    - Millstone III: Future Costs (Box 108:, Folder 3635-3636)
    - Movement for Economic Justice: Organizer Notebooks (Box 108:, Folder 3637-3638)
    - Northeast Utilities
      - General, 1980s and 1990s (Box 108:, Folder 3639)
      - General, 1983 (Box 108:, Folder 3640)
      - Abnormal Costs, 1981 (Box 108:, Folder 3641)
      - Conservation and Rate Structure, 1981 (Box 108:, Folder 3642)
      - Interest on December Accounts, 1982 (Box 108:, Folder 3643)
      - Issue Papers, 1983 (Box 108:, Folder 3644)
      - New Nuclear Units, 1981 (Box 108:, Folder 3645)
      - Official Paper, 1983 (Box 108:, Folder 3646)
      - Profits, 1981 (Box 109:, Folder 3647)
      - Relevant Interrogatories, 1983 (Box 109:, Folder 3648-3649)
      - Shutoffs, 1982 (Box 109:, Folder 3650-3652)
      - Public Service Company of New Hampshire Collapse (Box 109:, Folder 3653)
      - Seabrook (Box 109:, Folder 3654-3655)
        - Cost Estimate (Box 109:, Folder 3656-3657)
        - Post-Decision (Box 109:, Folder 3658)
        - Transcript Notes, 1983 (Box 109:, Folder 3659)
    - United Illuminating
      - General, 1972-1982 (Box 109:, Folder 3660)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 109:, Folder 3661-3662)
      - Net Present Value Runs, 1983 (Box 109:, Folder 3663-3664)
      - New Rates (Box 109:, Folder 3665)
      - Rate Hike Follow-up, 1983 (Box 109:, Folder 3666)
      - Relevant Interrogatories, 1983 (Box 109:, Folder 3667-3668)
      - unspecified
        For further information on utility rate cases, see: Series I: Director's Records, Marc Caplan Files and Miles Rappoport Files;Series X: Mary Mushinky Files; Series XI: Environmental Issues, Julie Mannarino Files; Series XII: Energy Issues, National, Connecticut, Solar, and Publications; Series XIV: Consumer Issues; and Series XVI: Subject Files, Energy and Government.
- Series XIV: Consumer Issues, undated, 1971-1979
  - Accountability Session (Box 110:, Folder 3669)
  - Advertising (Box 110:, Folder 3670)
  - Advisory Committee: Title XIX (Box 110:, Folder 3671)
  - Ambulatory Care Task Force (Box 110:, Folder 3672)
  - Appropriations Committee Testimony, 1973 February 2 (Box 110:, Folder 3673)
  - Automobile (Box 110:, Folder 3674)
  - Auto Body Regulations (Box 110:, Folder 3675)
  - Banks (Box 110:, Folder 3676)
  - Better Business Bureau (Box 110:, Folder 3677)
  - Bottle Bill (Box 110:, Folder 3678)
  - Business (Box 110:, Folder 3679)
  - Caplan Book (Box 110:, Folder 3680)
  - Caplan Deposition, 1977 June 9 (Box 110:, Folder 3681)
  - Citizens Lobby (Box 110:, Folder 3682)
  - Coastal Area Management (Box 110:, Folder 3683)
  - Community Development, Hartford (Box 110:, Folder 3684)
  - Community Liaison Proposal (Box 110:, Folder 3685)
  - Community Organizations (Box 110:, Folder 3686)
  - Condominiums (Box 110:, Folder 3687)
  - Congress (Box 110:, Folder 3688)
  - Connecticut Citizen Research Group (CCRG) ( (Box 110:, Folder 3689-3690)
  - Conservation (Box 110:, Folder 3691)
  - Consumer Center Instruction (Box 110:, Folder 3692)
  - Consumer Education (Box 110:, Folder 3693)
  - Consumer Federation of America (Box 110:, Folder 3694)
  - Consumer Action Committee (Box 110:, Folder 3695)
  - Consumer, Miscellaneous (Box 110:, Folder 3696)
  - Consumer Product Safety (Box 110:, Folder 3697)
  - Consumer Protection Agency (Box 110:, Folder 3698-3700)
  - Cooperatives (Box 110:, Folder 3701)
  - Credit (Box 110:, Folder 3702)
  - Credit Bureaus: Hartford (Box 110:, Folder 3703)
  - Credit Cards (Box 110:, Folder 3704)
  - Credit Practices (Box 110:, Folder 3705)
  - Credit Practices Act (Box 110:, Folder 3706)
  - Daycare (Box 110:, Folder 3707)
  - Department of Commerce (Box 110:, Folder 3708)
  - Department of Consumer Protection (DCP)
    - Ethington Report (Box 110:, Folder 3709)
    - Legislative Program (Box 110:, Folder 3710)
    - Pilot Draft (Box 110:, Folder 3711)
    - Report, 1971 (Box 110:, Folder 3712)
    - Testimony (Box 110:, Folder 3713)
  - Department of Environmental Protection (Box 110:, Folder 3714)
  - Department of Planning (Box 110:, Folder 3715)
  - Department of Public Works (Box 110:, Folder 3716)
  - Drugs (Box 110:, Folder 3717-3718)
  - Drugs (Box 111:, Folder 3719-3725)
  - Dunne, Barbara (Box 111:, Folder 3726)
  - Endangered Species (Box 111:, Folder 3727)
  - Energy (Box 111:, Folder 3728)
  - Environment
    - General (Box 111:, Folder 3729)
    - Careers (Box 111:, Folder 3730)
    - Community (Box 111:, Folder 3731)
    - People and Groups (Box 111:, Folder 3732)
    - Protection (Box 111:, Folder 3733)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 111:, Folder 3734-3739)
    - Subcommittee of Agriculture and Wetlands (Box 111:, Folder 3740)
  - Fair Rent Commission (Box 111:, Folder 3741)
  - Fair Trade Act (Box 111:, Folder 3742)
  - Farmlands (Box 111:, Folder 3743)
  - Food (Box 111:, Folder 3744)
  - Food Stamps (Box 111:, Folder 3745)
  - Franchising Session, 1972 (Box 111:, Folder 3746)
  - Fraud (Box 111:, Folder 3747)
  - Funerals and Funeral Homes (Box 111:, Folder 3748)
  - General Correspondence (Box 111:, Folder 3749)
  - General Law Committee (Box 111:, Folder 3750)
  - Generic Drugs (Box 111:, Folder 3751)
  - Goods Repair Estimates, 1977 (Box 111:, Folder 3752)
  - Handicapped (Box 111:, Folder 3753)
  - Health
    - General (Box 111:, Folder 3754)
    - Health Committee (Box 111:, Folder 3755)
    - Costs (Box 111:, Folder 3756)
    - Hospital Cost Commission (Box 111:, Folder 3757)
    - Insurance (Box 111:, Folder 3758-3760)
    - Issues (Box 111:, Folder 3761-3762)
    - Professional Standards Review Council (Box 112:, Folder 3763)
    - Health System Agencies (Box 112:, Folder 3764)
  - High Schools Contacted (Box 112:, Folder 3765)
  - Home Solicitation (Box 112:, Folder 3766)
  - Housing (Box 112:, Folder 3767)
  - Hudson Bay Company (Box 112:, Folder 3768)
  - Information Line (Box 112:, Folder 3769)
  - Inland Wetlands (Box 112:, Folder 3770)
  - Insurance (Box 112:, Folder 3771-3773)
  - Investment Income (Box 112:, Folder 3774)
  - Landlord/Tenant (Box 112:, Folder 3775)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 112:, Folder 3776)
  - Legislation, 1972-1978 (Box 112:, Folder 3777-3782)
  - Legislative (Box 112:, Folder 3783-3784)
  - Licensing (Box 112:, Folder 3785)
  - Literature: Miscellaneous (Box 112:, Folder 3786)
  - Lobbying (Box 112:, Folder 3787)
  - Long Island Sound (Box 112:, Folder 3788-3789)
  - Low Income Issues (Box 112:, Folder 3790)
  - Malls (Box 112:, Folder 3791)
  - Marine Environment (Box 112:, Folder 3792)
  - Massachusetts Fair Share (Box 112:, Folder 3793)
  - Maximum Finance Charge (Box 112:, Folder 3794)
  - Meat and Poultry (Box 112:, Folder 3795)
  - Media Air Pollution Proposal (Box 112:, Folder 3796)
  - Meeker, John (Box 112:, Folder 3797)
  - Meetings (Box 112:, Folder 3798)
  - Miscellaneous Issues (Box 112:, Folder 3799)
  - Mitchell College (Box 112:, Folder 3800)
  - Mobile Homes (Box 112:, Folder 3801)
  - Money Store, The (Box 112:, Folder 3802)
  - Money Taken In (Box 112:, Folder 3803)
  - Mortgages (Box 112:, Folder 3804)
  - Moving (Box 112:, Folder 3805)
  - Mystic (Box 112:, Folder 3806)
  - Nader, Ralph (Box 112:, Folder 3807)
  - National Center for Appropriate Technology (Box 112:, Folder 3808)
  - National PIRG Clearinghouse Material (Box 112:, Folder 3809)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Committee Proposal (Box 113:, Folder 3810)
  - Neighborhood Legal Services (Box 113:, Folder 3811)
  - Norwalk Economic Opportunity Now, Inc. (NEON) Training Agreement (Box 113:, Folder 3812)
  - Noise (Box 113:, Folder 3813)
  - North River Navigator (Box 113:, Folder 3814)
  - Nuclear Power (Box 113:, Folder 3815)
  - Nutrition Proposal (Box 113:, Folder 3816)
  - Office Policy (Box 113:, Folder 3817)
  - Ombudsman (Box 113:, Folder 3818)
  - Organizing Organizations (Box 113:, Folder 3819-3823)
  - Other Groups (Box 113:, Folder 3824)
  - Outer Continental Shelf (Box 113:, Folder 3825)
  - Overhead Transmission Lines (Box 113:, Folder 3826)
  - PAC New Haven (Box 113:, Folder 3827)
  - Party Lever (Box 113:, Folder 3828)
  - Patronage (Box 113:, Folder 3829)
  - Pelligrino Study: Norwalk Harbor (Box 113:, Folder 3830)
  - Pensions (Box 113:, Folder 3831-3833)
  - Personnel (Box 113:, Folder 3834-3835)
  - Pesticide Proposal (Box 113:, Folder 3836)
  - Pharmaceutical Association of Connecticut (Box 113:, Folder 3837)
  - Plain Language Bell (Box 113:, Folder 3838)
  - Plainfield Dog Track (Box 113:, Folder 3839)
  - Planning Process, 1979 (Box 113:, Folder 3840)
  - Plymouth Wetlands Problem (Box 113:, Folder 3841)
  - Pollution Laws (Box 113:, Folder 3842)
  - Postal Service (Box 113:, Folder 3843)
  - Power Siting Legislation Report (Box 113:, Folder 3844)
  - Pre-paid Legal Insurance (Box 113:, Folder 3845)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1976 (Box 113:, Folder 3846)
  - Presidential Primary (Box 113:, Folder 3847)
  - Press (Box 114:, Folder 3848-3850)
  - Probate Court (Box 114:, Folder 3851)
  - Procedures (Box 114:, Folder 3852)
  - Professional Associations (Box 114:, Folder 3853)
  - Projects (Box 114:, Folder 3854)
  - Property Tax (Box 114:, Folder 3855)
  - Proposed Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 114:, Folder 3856-3857)
  - Public Act 490 (Box 114:, Folder 3858)
  - Public Citizen (Box 114:, Folder 3859)
  - Public Health and Safety (Box 114:, Folder 3860)
  - Public Interest Lobby (Box 114:, Folder 3861)
  - Public Interest Research Groups (PIRG's) (Box 114:, Folder 3862-3864)
  - Public Members 1602 (Box 114:, Folder 3865-3866)
  - Public Participation in Federal Proceedings (Box 114:, Folder 3867)
  - Public Service Announcements (PSA's) (Box 114:, Folder 3868)
  - Publication Lists and Letters (Box 114:, Folder 3869)
  - Pyramid Sales (Box 114:, Folder 3870)
  - Railroads (Box 114:, Folder 3871)
  - Real Estate Mortgages (Box 114:, Folder 3872)
  - Reardon, Ken (Box 114:, Folder 3873)
  - Recycling (Box 114:, Folder 3874)
  - Redlining (Box 114:, Folder 3875)
  - Regulatory Reform (Box 114:, Folder 3876)
  - Rentex Information (Box 114:, Folder 3877)
  - Representations of Guarantees, 1973 (Box 114:, Folder 3878)
  - Research Department (Box 114:, Folder 3879)
  - Resource Development (Box 114:, Folder 3880)
  - Revenue Sharing (Box 114:, Folder 3881)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham (Box 114:, Folder 3882)
  - Rogol, Marty (Box 114:, Folder 3883)
  - Rome, Lewis (Box 114:, Folder 3884)
  - Saccharin (Box 114:, Folder 3885)
  - Sarasin, Ronald (Box 115:, Folder 3886)
  - Satellite Communications (Box 115:, Folder 3887)
  - School Buses (Box 115:, Folder 3888)
  - School Financing (Box 115:, Folder 3889)
  - School of Law (Box 115:, Folder 3890)
  - Secretary of State (Box 115:, Folder 3891)
  - Self Service Gas Stations (Box 115:, Folder 3892)
  - Senior Citizens (Box 115:, Folder 3893)
  - Sewage Treatment Priorities (Box 115:, Folder 3894)
  - Schuchman, Helvah (Box 115:, Folder 3895)
  - Small Claims Court (Box 115:, Folder 3896-3901)
  - Smoke Detectors (Box 115:, Folder 3902)
  - Smoking Laws (Box 115:, Folder 3903)
  - Social Services (Box 115:, Folder 3904)
  - Solar Energy (Box 115:, Folder 3905-3906)
  - Solid Waste Disposal (Box 115:, Folder 3907)
  - SNET: Rate Increase (Box 115:, Folder 3908)
  - Southeastern Connecticut (Box 115:, Folder 3909)
  - Space Heaters (Box 115:, Folder 3910)
  - Spay Clinics (Box 115:, Folder 3911)
  - Stamford Chapter (Box 115:, Folder 3912)
  - State
    - Budget (Box 115:, Folder 3913)
    - Government (Box 115:, Folder 3914)
    - Leasing (Box 115:, Folder 3915)
  - Statutory Research (Box 115:, Folder 3916)
  - Stevens, J.P. (Box 115:, Folder 3917)
  - Sun Day (Box 115:, Folder 3918)
  - Support Center (Box 115:, Folder 3919)
  - Surgical Centers (Box 115:, Folder 3920-3921)
  - Swine Flue Program (Box 115:, Folder 3922)
  - Syz, Steve (Box 115:, Folder 3923)
  - Tax, National Commission (Box 115:, Folder 3924)
  - Tax Proposal (Box 115:, Folder 3925-3926)
  - Tax Proposal (Box 116:, Folder 3927)
  - Tax Reform (Box 116:, Folder 3928)
  - Taxes (Box 116:, Folder 3929)
  - Taxpayer's Coalition (Box 116:, Folder 3930)
  - Telephone Fundraising (Box 116:, Folder 3931)
  - Telephone Toll Calls (Box 116:, Folder 3932)
  - Toll Free Call Regions (Box 116:, Folder 3933)
  - Television (Box 116:, Folder 3934)
  - Testimony, 1973 (Box 116:, Folder 3935-3936)
  - Ticket Sales (Box 116:, Folder 3937)
  - Title 20 (Box 116:, Folder 3938)
  - Toy Safety (Box 116:, Folder 3939)
  - Transcript Coding (Box 116:, Folder 3940)
  - Transportation (Box 116:, Folder 3941)
  - Transportation Control Plan Letter (Box 116:, Folder 3942)
  - Transportation Proposal (Box 116:, Folder 3943)
  - Traveler's Insurance (Box 116:, Folder 3944)
  - Truth in Lending (Box 116:, Folder 3945)
  - Upper Albany Community Organization (UACO) (Box 116:, Folder 3946)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW) (Box 116:, Folder 3947-3949)
  - Unfair Trade Practices (Box 116:, Folder 3950)
  - Uniform Consumer Credit Code (Box 116:, Folder 3951)
  - University Product Code (Box 116:, Folder 3952)
  - Utilities
    - General (Box 116:, Folder 3953)
    - Utilities Coalition (Box 116:, Folder 3954-3955)
    - Settlements (Box 116:, Folder 3956)
    - Shut-offs (Box 116:, Folder 3957)
  - Volunteer (Box 116:, Folder 3958)
  - Voting Rights (Box 116:, Folder 3959)
  - WFSB - Channel 3 (Box 116:, Folder 3960)
  - WNBC - TV 4 (Box 116:, Folder 3961)
  - WPOP (Box 116:, Folder 3962)
  - Warranties (Box 116:, Folder 3963)
  - Washington Correspondence (Box 117:, Folder 3964)
  - Waterbury Citizen Action Group (Box 117:, Folder 3965)
  - Water Company Lands (Box 117:, Folder 3966)
  - Water Pollution (Box 117:, Folder 3967)
  - Welfare (Box 117:, Folder 3968)
  - Wellington Industries, Inc. (Box 117:, Folder 3969)
  - West Haven (Box 117:, Folder 3970)
  - West Hartford (Box 117:, Folder 3971)
  - Wetlands (Box 117:, Folder 3972)
  - Work Study (Box 117:, Folder 3973)
  - Women's Rights (Box 117:, Folder 3974)
  - Xerox (Box 117:, Folder 3975)
  - Yearbooks (Box 117:, Folder 3976)
  - Yoakum, Robert and Alice (Box 117:, Folder 3977)
  - Consumer Complaints
    - Consumer Complaints Center (Box 118:, Folder 3978)
    - Phone-ins (Box 118:, Folder 3979)
    - Complaints
    - A (Box 118:, Folder 3980)
    - B (Box 118:, Folder 3981)
    - C (Box 118:, Folder 3982-3983)
    - D (Box 118:, Folder 3984-3985)
    - E (Box 118:, Folder 3986)
    - F (Box 118:, Folder 3987)
    - G (Box 118:, Folder 3988)
    - H (Box 118:, Folder 3989)
    - I (Box 118:, Folder 3990)
    - J (Box 118:, Folder 3991)
    - K (Box 118:, Folder 3992)
    - L (Box 118:, Folder 3993)
    - M (Box 118:, Folder 3994-3995)
    - N (Box 118:, Folder 3996)
    - O (Box 118:, Folder 3997)
    - R (Box 118:, Folder 3998)
    - S (Box 118:, Folder 3999-4000)
    - T (Box 119:, Folder 4001)
    - U (Box 119:, Folder 4002)
    - V (Box 119:, Folder 4003)
    - W (Box 119:, Folder 4004)
    - X (Box 119:, Folder 4005)
    - Y (Box 119:, Folder 4006)
      For further information on consumer issues, see: Series I: Director's Records, Marc Caplan Files and Miles Rappoport Files; and Series XVI: Subject Files.
- Series XV: Lobbying Efforts, undated, 1982-1984
  - Ad Hoc Neighborhood Development Plan (Box 120:, Folder 4007)
  - Anti-racism Coalition of Connecticut (ARCC) (Box 120:, Folder 4008)
  - 1983 August 27 (Box 120:, Folder 4009)
  - Benvenuto Meeting (Box 120:, Folder 4010)
  - Blue Hills (Box 120:, Folder 4011)
  - Blue Hills Citizen Action Group (CHCAG) ( (Box 120:, Folder 4012-4018)
  - Bonding: Street Repair (Box 120:, Folder 4019)
  - Bristol: Organizing Issues (Box 120:, Folder 4020)
  - Bulletin, 1977 (Box 120:, Folder 4021-4023)
  - Bulletin, 1978 (Box 120:, Folder 4024-4026)
  - Citizen Action (Box 120:, Folder 4027)
  - Citizen Lobby (Box 120:, Folder 4028-4032)
  - City Council, 1983 (Box 120:, Folder 4033)
  - City Manager's Office, 1983 (Box 120:, Folder 4034)
  - CCAG Report (Box 120:, Folder 4035)
  - Connecticut Labor Energy Coalition (Box 120:, Folder 4036)
  - Consumer Petition (Box 120:, Folder 4037)
  - Crime/Police (Box 120:, Folder 4038)
  - Demographics (Box 120:, Folder 4039)
  - Department of Public Works (Box 120:, Folder 4040)
  - Deregulation (Box 120:, Folder 4041)
  - Dogs (Box 120:, Folder 4042)
  - Doorknocking Notes, 1983 (Box 120:, Folder 4043)
  - East Hartford, South Windsor, Manchester Regions (Box 120:, Folder 4044)
  - Education
    - General, 1982 (Box 120:, Folder 4045)
    - Literature, 1983-1984 (Box 120:, Folder 4046)
    - Out Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 120:, Folder 4047)
  - Enterprise zones (Box 120:, Folder 4048)
  - Electoral: BHCAG, PAC (Box 120:, Folder 4048)
  - Federal Transit Money (Box 120:, Folder 4050)
  - Fair Budget Action Committee Conference, 1983 (Box 120:, Folder 4051)
  - Freeze (Box 120:, Folder 4052)
  - Gas Deregulation (Box 121:, Folder 4053-4055)
  - Governor's Forum, 1982 April 3 (Box 121:, Folder 4056)
  - Grappo Meeting (Box 121:, Folder 4057)
  - Graphics (Box 121:, Folder 4058)
  - Grants (Box 121:, Folder 4059)
  - Greater Hartford Black Democratic Club (Box 121:, Folder 4060)
  - Greater Hartford Community Labor Alliance (Box 121:, Folder 4061)
  - Handbook Paste-up (Box 121:, Folder 4062)
  - Handbook Update (Box 121:, Folder 4063)
  - Hart (Box 121:, Folder 4064)
  - Housing (Box 121:, Folder 4065)
  - How To Lobby (Box 121:, Folder 4066)
  - In-mail From City Council Representatives (Box 121:, Folder 4067)
  - Interns (Box 121:, Folder 4068)
  - League of Women Voters (LWV) (Box 121:, Folder 4069)
  - Lease (Box 121:, Folder 4070)
  - Legislation, 1982 (Box 121:, Folder 4071)
  - Legislation Fact Sheets, 1983 (Box 121:, Folder 4072)
  - Legislative Alerts (Box 121:, Folder 4073)
  - Legislative Newsletter (Box 121:, Folder 4074)
  - Lobby Coordinators Information (Box 121:, Folder 4075)
  - Lobbying for Fun and Non-Profit (Box 121:, Folder 4076)
  - Lobby Revision (Box 121:, Folder 4077)
  - Minutes (Box 121:, Folder 4078)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 121:, Folder 4079)
  - Newington (Box 121:, Folder 4080)
  - Newsletter: Other States (Box 121:, Folder 4081)
  - People Lobby: California (Box 121:, Folder 4082)
  - Phone Maps (Box 121:, Folder 4083)
  - Phone Wheels Cover Letter (Box 121:, Folder 4084)